good morning and let's look at the top
five stocks to watch out for in trade
today so starting with the earnings you
know which have been boring in and
earning season has begun so first we'll
have Tata Communications which posted
its earnings last evening the Q3 numbers
have been a good set of numbers for Tata
communication overall the Consolidated
revenue for the company remained flat
which around
4,223 clor and mainly the growth in the
revenue was led uh by the data business
uh growth which has compensated the
decrease in the voice business which
data communication saw so that's why we
seeing a flattish growth as both these
were balancing each other so that is why
the increase in Data Business balance
the decrease in voice business for the
company talking about the profits of the
company the profitability of the company
has seen a surely a very very strong
growth a 5.2 times uh growth 2x growth
on a year onye basis is what we're
seeing that's almost 4,
428 up the profits are 428 up on a year
on year basis so let's look at the
profit number that's 309 CR for this
quarter versus uh Q3 f520 it was only 59
CR so let's see a good good growth in
the bottom line of the company and that
is obviously surely leading to a good
overall performance for the company as
well uh talking about the uh iita
margins and iita of the company uh we're
seeing the IIT is coming at 1,46 CR uh
which is a growth of around 37 .5% on a
year on-ear basis obviously this growth
is obviously led by a robust growth and
margin expansion in the data business as
well as the cost optimization measures
which the company have taken has taken
is what is something that is leading to
a better margins and the better AA
performance as well operational
performance of the company so all in all
a good set of numbers by data
Communications moving on to ICI Lombard
overall we're seeing a good set of
numbers by the company the
profitabilities up by
6.8% uh we're seeing that the combined
ratio of the company is also at 97.9%
versus
98.7% on a year on year basis net
profits up by 7% solvency ratio at
2.76% uh 2.76 times versus 2.18 times on
a year on year basis and the gross
written premium which we normally look
out for in these companies is at up by
9% it's coming at 4,000 around 4,100
gross versus
3,769 draw on a year on your basis so
surely we are seeing a good Improvement
coming in for um the company as well ICI
Lombard a decent set of numbers by ICI
Lombard moving on to another company
that is posted with numbers is L&T
infotech revenues up by 5.1% on a
quarter on quarter basis you normally
compare quarter on quarter basis for it
companies uh so it is at
3,152 cres versus 2,900
98 gross profitability jump has jumped
up by 14% overall uh the dollar revenue
is also up by 5.8% and it is coming at4
27.8
million versus U uh uh overall in a
quarter on quarter basis we're seeing a
good growth for the company now let's
talk about
uh margins of the company the IIT
margins for L&T infotech are at 20.6%
versus 19.9% so good uh performance on
the operational front as well and uh
surely going to keep the stock in Focus
today we have India Indian bank which is
in Focus as the board has uh considered
to and approved the proposal for raising
funds uh or Equity you could say Equity
capital for the bank by either qip FBO
or right issue and this will the board
is going to meet on 22nd January to
consider this and approve this matter so
let's keep an eye out on that obviously
uh we do have a lot of earnings coming
in and Nifty we do have baj the Bajaj
twins baj finance and baj fer which will
be boting their earnings so let's keep
an eye out on that as well as we do have
an others HDFC AMC Federal Bank uh V uh
vsg industri sterlite Tech hav Hindustan
zinc are some of the important earnings
which will be coming out today so let's
keep an eye out on all these earnings as
well